#### Contact

ssahasrabhojane@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prathameshsahasrabhojane-4b3b12148 (LinkedIn) prathameshsahasrabhojane.web.app/ (Personal) www.technoaddict.in (Blog)

#### Top Skills

Android Development Unity3D AR System

#### Certifications

Android Development Internship Certified C Programmer

#### Honors-Awards

AICTE Vishwakrma Awards 2018
Equinox Winner
Best Research Paper Award
Top Scorer in Voice Based Payment
Hackathon (NPCI)

#### **Publications**

Recommendation for data migration

# Prathamesh Sahasrabhojane

Ninja Developer | Full Stack Developer | Flutter Developer | Amazon Alexa Developer | WebGL Developer

Nasik, Maharashtra, India

## Summary

Experienced Android Developer skilled in Unity3D, AR System (Augmented Reality), and Mixed Reality. Strong engineering professional with a Diploma Engineering focused in Computer Engineering Technologies.

Al assistant enthusiast worked on Google Assistant and Amazon Alexa.

### Experience

Flutter by Google Developer December 2018 - Present

Self Employed Mixed Reality Developer September 2018 - Present

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Developer
August 2018 - Present

Self-employed Google Actions Developer June 2018 - Present India

Self-employed Android Developer June 2013 - Present India

Self employed Android Developer May 2013 - Present

Netspaceindia Mobile Application Developer May 2017 - June 2017 (2 months) Nashik

Worked as Mobile Application Development Intern.

Self employed Blogger June 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 1 month) Nasik Area, India

## Education

Sandip Foundations Sandip Institute of Technology & Research Centre, P.O.Mahirawani, Dist.Nashik
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2018 - 2021)

K. K. Wagh Polytechnic

High School Diploma, Computer Science · (2016 - 2018)